iwebtrack.com 2018-04-10

# Privacy Policy at iWebTrack

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

iWebTrack respects your privacy and guards your data carefully. We realize that the exciting growth of the Internet and online services has also brought concern for consumers about what information is collected about them. We want you to know that we apply our long-standing commitment to safeguarding privacy to all of our online and Internet activities.

iWebTrack does not share, disclose or sell any personally identifiable information collected online with other companies or organizations, nor does iWebTrack make or accept any offers to market products through iWebTrack to members or end-users. iWebTrack does not disclose any customer information, including your website address, to any party for any reason. iWebTrack does not market to children or collect personal information about children at this site.

iWebTrack may ask you for some personally identifiable information about you when you are at our site, such as your name, telephone number or email address. We use this information to help maintain accurate accounts, provide the service you've requested, bill/pay correctly, answer your inquiries, and market services and products to you. iWebTrack may also include information about your visit to our site in aggregated data that does not identify you specifically, in order to help make our site more useful to you and for our own geographical and statistical tracking purposes.

For example: 

  * Our server recognizes your domain name and the pages that you visit. This data is gathered in an aggregate manner for quality control and improvement of our site.  
 
  * When you send us email, we use your email address so we can respond to your inquiry.  
 
  * We collect information that you volunteer to us on surveys and job applications, as well as contest and registration sites.  
 
  * We also ask for your email address to communicate with you in the future about your account and other iWebTrack-affiliated products and services. We sometimes ask for other information for more particular purposes, such as the postal address used to send you a product you ordered.  

We use strong technology to ensure that your sensitive information is secure and protected from unauthorized access or improper use. For example, you will note that while using some features of the iWebTrack website and online services, you will need to submit a password or some other type of personally identifiable information.

You may review or update the available personally identifiable information that we've received from you online by contacting iWebTrack at the address below. To better safeguard your information, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identify before granting access or making corrections in your information. iWebTrack has developed this privacy policy in accordance with current U.S. standards.

For questions regarding the above policy, contact [privacy@iwebtrack.com](mailto:privacy@iwebtrack.com?subject=iWebTrack%20Privacy%20Inquiry)

|   
|  |   
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
|  | Try it on your site free  
---  
Try our web analytics service **free** for 30 days with no obligation, and no limit to the number of websites you manage.

Try It Free

|  |
